And if you are lucky there is someone there, someone else in the audience
who thinks: This seemed to be an interesting person or that was an interesting question
So you are lucky then maybe someone will come and talk to you afterwards
And say, yes, it was a good question, yeah what exciting ...
What brave of you that you dared to talk even though you don't have Swedish as your native language
Do you understand, there are no guarantees.
I can't promise it will happen but
If you should have the chance to meet people and talk to people
So you have to go to racks
where there are other people
and at least give people the chance to come up and talk to you
so you just got a little luck